MUHAMMED IRSHAD K

Web Developer

+91 73 5626 4323 ♦ Pallikkal Bazar, Kerala, India

mialungal@gmail.com ♦ http://www.linkedin.com/in/irshad-alungal ♦ https://irshad-alungal.github.io/web/

OBJECTIVE

Web Developer 2+ years of experience in front-end, to build a career in the field of front-end developer and to explore me fully with which I can increase my potential to work effectively in the field of front-end developer. I would like to constantly upgrade my knowledge and skills with every opportunity.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Mechanical, Abdul Kalam Technological University At KMCT College of Engineering, Calicut.

2019 - 2022

Diploma in Mechanical, Government of Kerala State Board of Technical Education

2015 - 2018

At KMCT Polytechnic College, Calicut.

SKILLS

Technical Skills HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, Angular, MongoDB, Tailwind, WordPress

Software Skills VS Code, Netlify, GitHub, Git, MS Office, AutoCAD

Other Skills Communication, Problem-solving, Time management, Leadership

EXPERIENCE

Web DeveloperSep 2023 - PresentNINETYSIX SolutionsDubai - Remote

- Front-End Development
- Responsive Web Designing
- API Fetching

Technical AssistantXandY Learning
Aug 2022 - June 2023
Calicut – Full Time

- Managing Web and App
- Class Embedding
- Co-ordinator of Mentors
- Generate admit card using Google Script
- Generate progress reports using word & Excel mailings connection

PROJECTS

I have successfully completed diverse web development projects utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and WordPress. All of my innovative projects are showcased in detail on my portfolio website (https://irshad-alungal.github.io/web/), providing a comprehensive overview of my skills and accomplishments. Feel free to explore my work by clicking the link or scanning the provided QR code.



ACHIEVEMENT

- I got two National level awards for my project design from National Level Project Competition SRISHTI'22
 organized by Saintgits College of Engineering, Kottayam. The project is titled Design and Fabrication of UV
 Dryer.
 - Best SolidWorks Project
 - Best Analytical Project
- Fi-Pro challenge winner (front-end challenge) organized by TinkerHub KMCT (Click Here)

I hereby declare that the above-furnished information is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.